<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>WCNN</title><subtitle>A minimal, responsive, and powerful Jekyll theme for presenting professional writing.</subtitle> <updated>2022-09-19T22:51:38+00:00</updated> <author> <name>English Class</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 English Class </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Aston Martin</title><link href="/posts/test-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aston Martin" /><published>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/test-1/</id> <content src="/posts/test-1/" /> <author> <name>Me</name> </author> <category term="Articles" /> <summary> The Aston Martin Valhalla is one of the most recent hypercars in development. It’s a mid-engined hybrid built car with the help of formula 1 technology. It is powered by a 4.0 litre twin-turbo V8 engine that can produce over 7200rpm (revolutions per minute). The Valhalla has been made too easy to drive, with space for luggage behind the seats, a centre console and a phone mount for the driver.... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>All Blacks vs Ireland</title><link href="/posts/test-1-Copy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All Blacks vs Ireland" /><published>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/test-1-Copy/</id> <content src="/posts/test-1-Copy/" /> <author> <name>Te Koha Gordon</name> </author> <category term="Report" /> <summary> All Blacks vs Ireland- Te Koha Gordon All Blacks vs Ireland ( 42-19 ) The Allblack won against Ireland on the 3rd of July at Eden park, Auckland, in the first game of the Steinlager series. It was a revenge game from what happened last year in Dublin. It was great determination from both sides with Ireland early on making metres from finding the holes in the All blacks defence, but it ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Protein Powder</title><link href="/posts/test-1-Copy-(4)/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Protein Powder" /><published>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/test-1-Copy-(4)/</id> <content src="/posts/test-1-Copy-(4)/" /> <author> <name>CBum</name> </author> <category term="Information" /> <summary> Creatine and Protein powder It is not crack. Even if it looks like it, it is not </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Deforestation</title><link href="/posts/test-1-Copy-(3)/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deforestation" /><published>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/test-1-Copy-(3)/</id> <content src="/posts/test-1-Copy-(3)/" /> <author> <name>Luca Dapas</name> </author> <category term="Articles" /> <summary> Deforestation- Luca Dapas We Need To Act On Deforestation What is deforestation? What’s happening to the Amazon rainforest? These are questions you may be pondering in your mind. As you witness on social media the terrorising situations that so many people and species alike are experiencing due to the selfish and cruel actions of some major brands, trying to make some extra dough. Imagine t... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Death Penalty</title><link href="/posts/test-1-Copy-(2)/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Death Penalty" /><published>2001-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2001-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/test-1-Copy-(2)/</id> <content src="/posts/test-1-Copy-(2)/" /> <author> <name>Oliver Grace</name> </author> <category term="Articles" /> <summary> In this article, I will be jumping off the edge of a cliff and diving head first into the thrilling yet chilling topic of the death penalty. First off, what is the death penalty? Well, the death penalty is a criminal offence punishable by death - it is a very serious, yet uniquely interesting topic. As I have explained this is a punishment of the highest living order. However, this may come ... </summary> </entry> </feed>
